Adams, Leonard India Files 5333
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Leonard Adams India Files
1945-1964
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Adams, Leonard
5333
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents), case files.
This collection of information on India was donated by Leonard Adams.
5603953
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, September 15, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3046: Leonard P. Adams Papers /4008: Leonard P. Adams Additional Files
Adams, Leonard.
5603953
- Labor & Industrial Relations Topics- News, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Manpower Problems - Newsp. Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Articles on Particular Industries-News, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Statistical Data - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- General Business Conditions - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agriculture, Food & the Like - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Commentaries on Govt. & other matters, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Education - Clippings, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Adams-Vaid Project, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Labor - General, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Indust. Relations Research Topics - General, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Absenteeism, 1948-1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- D.G.E.T., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Area Study - Manpower Institute, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Madras Study, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Economic Times, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Mr. Leonard P. Adams (Box 1, Folder 17)
- India Newspaper Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- IIE Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Scope and Contents
  Japanese
- Institute of Labor Relations Research, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Banerjee, 1945-1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Manpower Institute, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Pamphlets, 1958-1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Coding System, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Reports, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)